(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
待たれよ。
Wait up.
ニコニコ。
Smiley.
あらあら。
Ara ara.
はにゃ？
Hanya?
眠たい。
I'm sleepy.
チョコも眠たい。
Choco is sleepy too.
チョコ...
Choco...
待て待て待て待て！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
ガチ？
For real?
やだやだやだやだー！
No, no, no, noooo!
どうも、ホロライブ2期生、悪魔でバーチャル保健医、癒月ちょこです！
Hello, Hololive 2nd Gen, an evil virtual school nurse, Yuzuki Choco-desu!
お前何言うちゃ？
What are you saying?
サンキュースパチャ！
Thank you, super chat!
サンキューベリーマッチ！
Thank you very much!
オラ、豚、登って。頑張って、豚。
Hey, pig, climb. Do your best, pig.
オラ、豚、こっちよこっち。どっち？
Hey, pig, over here, over here. Which way?
はいはいはい。
Yes, yes, yes.
なんだろう。
I wonder what it is.
何年やってると思ってるんですか。うぃー！
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Whee!
先生に向かってなんですか、その言葉遣いは。
What's with that tone towards your teacher?
友達じゃないんですよ。いいですか？
We're not friends. Got it?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね。
I'm Yuzuki Choco-sensei, after all.
あ、やばい、うわー！
Ah, oh no, uwaa!
美味しかったの？
Was it delicious?
あ、違う！ダメ！あー！
Ah, no! Stop! Ahhh!
ちょこしかおらん。
There's only Choco.
なんか動いた！なんだあいつ！
Something moved! What is that guy!?
はい、いらっしゃいませ。
Yes, welcome.
チョコ聞き専よ。聞き専！
Choco is just listening. Just listening!
ねぇー！
Hey!
おやすみ。
Good night.
よしっ。
Alright.
はぁ〜、いい天気。
Ha~, such nice weather.
ちょこせんせーしょん
作詞・作曲・編曲：周防パトラ
Choco-sen-Sensation!
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Suo Patra
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい。
I want to take a nap in the nurse's office bed.
ズル休み　許されない
Skipping school isn't allowed
保健室は神聖なの
The nurse's office is sacred
サボってる　ちょっとだけ
誰も来なきゃやる気出ない
I'm slacking off, just a little
I'm not motivated if no one comes
チョコチョコせんせーしょん(Yay!)
Choco-Choco-Sensation (Yay!)
チョコチョコせんせーしょん
Choco-Choco-Sensation
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
At this rate, I'll be hopeless
はぁ　起きなきゃ　太るから
2回目なあくび　おやすみなさい
Haa, I gotta get up, or I'll get fat
A second yawn, good night
ごめんなさい　少しだけ寝かせて
先生モード　シャットダウン
I'm sorry, let me sleep just a bit more
Teacher mode, shut down
夢見る　フワフワ
ずっとこうして眠りたい
Dreaming fluffy dreams
I want to keep sleeping like this forever
ありがとう　ポカポカ
ちょっと休憩してるだけ
Thank you, warm and cozy
I'm just taking a little break
ゆだん大敵ね
急に君が来るなんて
Carelessness is a great enemy
To think you'd suddenly show up
ねぇ、どこか悪いの？
Hey, is something wrong?
なにか期待しているのかな？
Are you expecting something, I wonder?
揺らぐ心　巡る感情
口どけ甘い　セッション
A wavering heart, circling emotions
A session that melts sweetly in the mouth
癒されたい？甘えていたい？
だめよ　おちょこせんせーしょん
Do you want to be healed? Do you want to be pampered?
No, no, O-Choco-Sensation
君の視線　君の体温
分かっても恋は　量れない
Your gaze, your body heat
Even if I understand them, I can't measure love
元気なのに　溜息しちゃうの
もしかして何かの病？
Even though I'm fine, I end up sighing
Could it be some kind of illness?
胸ドキドキするまで動けないから
トキメキ運んできて　My Cupids
I can't move until my heart thumps
Bring me heart-fluttering moments, My Cupids
ズル休み　また来たの？
Skipping school? Did you come again?
保健室は神聖なの
The nurse's office is sacred
サボってた　ちょっとだけ
やっぱり君に居て欲しい
I was slacking off, just a little
After all, I want you to be here
明日は週末　おやすみなさいだよ
Tomorrow is the weekend, it's 'good night'
家飲み！
Drinking at home!
最高！
The best!
引きこもり！
Shut-in!
最高！
The best!
もちろんノーメイク
Of course, no makeup
ハイ！
Hai!
休みになったら　白衣脱ぎます
When the holiday comes, I'll take off my lab coat
さぁ全てを見せて
シャンピン！　堪能できないじゃん
Now, show me everything
Champine! I can't even enjoy it
何を隠してるの？
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
What are you hiding?
I can hear the speed of your heartbeat
見せて心　巡る熱を
平常保ってる　現状層
Show me your heart, the circling heat
A status layer that keeps things normal
愛されたい？頼られたい？
かまってよ　おちょこせんせーしょん
Do you want to be loved? Do you want to be relied on?
Pay attention to me, O-Choco-Sensation
君の重み　君の匂い
分かっても愛は　量れない
Your weight, your scent
Even if I understand them, I can't measure love
大好きだから　溜息しちゃうよ
やっぱりそれは　恋の病
Because I love you so much, I end up sighing
After all, it is love sickness
胸ドキドキするまで動けないから
トキメキ運んできて　My Cupids
I can't move until my heart thumps
Bring me heart-fluttering moments, My Cupids
混ざり合った　この世界だって
Even in this world where things are all mixed together
みんな癒やしが必要だから
Everyone needs healing
チョコチョコせんせーしょん(Yay!)
Choco-Choco-Sensation (Yay!)
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to make you hopeless too
揺らぐ心 巡る感情 口どけ甘いセーしょん
Wavering hearts, revolving emotions, a sweet melting sensation
癒されたい 甘えていたい 頼ってよ ちょこセーしょん
Wanting to be healed, wanting to be pampered, lean on me, Choco Sensation
君の視線 君の体温 分かっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your body temperature, even if I know them, love can't be measured
元気なのにダメージしちゃう もしかしてもう手遅れ?
Even though I'm fine, I'm taking damage, maybe it's already too late?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて 夢中で
But I can't move until my heart starts racing, so bring me that excitement, as I'm head over heels
チョコチョコ セーしょん イェイ! チョコチョコ セーしょん イェイ!
Choco-Choco Sensation, Yay! Choco-Choco Sensation, Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you too
はい! ということで 癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026...
Yes! And so, Yuzuki Choco's Birthday Celebration 2026...
...始まりましたー!
...has begun!
見て見て! 1曲目から ちょこ 生まれ変わりましたー!
Look, look! From the very first song, Choco has been reborn!
いやー 今日はね 原点回帰 ということで...
Well, today is a "return to roots," so...
...ちょこの なんと 保健室ステージなの!
...it's Choco's... wait for it... Health Room stage!
いや ちょっと保健室も ちょっと生まれ変わって...
The Health Room has also been reborn a bit...
...めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりましたー!
...and it's become super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとか できそうだよね。
It looks like we could do situation dramas here.
今日は 生まれ変わった ニューちょこと 素敵なね...
Today, with this reborn New Choco...
...ゲスト様を いっぱい呼んで ライブをしていくんだけど
...I've invited many wonderful guests to perform a live show
その前に みんなちょこのこと もっと見たいよね?
But before that, you all want to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも まだダメだよ。
Ah, but not yet.
これから来る お二人に ちょこの撮影会を ご依頼しちゃいましたー!
I've asked the two people who are about to arrive to hold a photo session for Choco!
それでは 早速呼んでいきましょう。
Well then, let's call them out right away.
ノエル様! ラミィ様ー!
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
きたよー!
We're here!
せーの!
One, two!
ちょこ先生 お誕生日 おめでとう!!
Happy Birthday, Choco-sensei!!
ということで今回はね この可愛い両手に花で...
So this time, with these two cuties by my side...
...可愛いお二人に ちょっとね ちょこの撮影会をしてってもらおうと思うんですけど
...I'd like them to hold a photo session for Choco
まずは 自己紹介 よろしくお願いします。
But first, please introduce yourselves.
ノイちゃんから!
Starting with Noi-chan!
はい! えー こんまっする! ホロライブ3期生の 白銀ノエルとー
Yes! Um, Kon-muscle! I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive's 3rd Generation...
はい! ホロライブ5期生の 顔が肝臓 雪花ラミィです!
Yes! I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive's 5th Generation, whose face is a liver!
今日は よろしくお願いします!
We're looking forward to being here today!
まぁね ちょっとちょこ先生の 本当に可愛くなったところ...
Well, since Choco-sensei has become truly cute...
...ちょっと団長 頑張って 攻めていこうと思いますので よろしくお願いします。
...this Knight Commander will do her best to capture that!
ラミィも 攻めるよね?
Lamy, you're going to go for it too, right?
ラミィも ギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います!
Lamy is also going to try and push the limits!
いや 撮影会やるなら ちょっとね この二人を呼ぶしかないかなーって思って...
Well, I thought if I'm going to have a photo session, I just HAD to invite these two...
...呼んじゃいました。
...so here they are.
いや しかも しかも ちょっと 後で この三人から なんと お知らせもあるみたいなので
And, and! It seems there's even an announcement from the three of us later...
撮影会の後で 皆様 楽しみにしててくださーい!
So please look forward to it after the photo session!
それじゃあ ちょっと こちらで 撮影会 よろしくお願いしまーす!
Well then, please start the photo session over here!
えほ! えほ! えほ! えほ! おー なんかすごいとこ来たぞ。
Yo-ho! Yo-ho! Yo-ho! Yo-ho! Oh, we've come to an amazing place.
ねえ、すごい! 可愛い!
Right? It's amazing! So cute!
可愛いでしょ 可愛いでしょ
Isn't it cute? Isn't it?
撮影会は ちょこの ここの 診察室でやりまーす!
We'll be doing the photo session here in Choco's consultation room!
かわいい！
So cute!
ね、かわいい。
Right? So cute.
でしょ、でしょ、でしょ。
Right? Right? Right?
でもさ、診察室だけどベッドは？
But wait, this is a clinic, where's the bed?
ベッドどこ？
Where's the bed?
ベッド？あ、本当だ。
The bed? Oh, you're right.
あ、何？
Oh, what's this?
パネルもある。あれ使う？
There's a panel too. Do we use that?
あ、ちょっ、そこ！絶対ダメ！
Ah, wait, not there! That's definitely off-limits!
え、これダメなの？
Eh, this is no good?
そこは後のメン限で使うの。
I'm saving that for the members-only stream later.
あー何？メン限！
Oh, what? Members-only!
メン限、メン限。
Members-only, members-only.
えーちょっとね、ベッドとか、ちょっと色々、
Well, you know, with the bed and all,
撮影会とか、シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって思って。
I was thinking of doing a photo shoot or a situation drama.
シチュエーションドラマ！
A situation drama!
とんでもないことしようとしてる！
She's planning something outrageous!
本当だよ。
For real.
Yes, そうなんですよ。
Yes, exactly.
まーまー、まーそれは置いといて。
Anyway, setting that aside for now.
ちょっと今回は、二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので。
Since I'd like you two to do the photography this time...
まずは、
First off,
分かりました。
Understood.
シュッ、シュッ。撮りますよ。よいしょ。
*Swish, swish* I'm taking them. Here we go.
ラミィ様には、
For Lamy-sama...
お、カメラ！
Oh, a camera!
え、本格的な！すごい、カメラ来た！
Eh, a professional one! Wow, the camera's here!
そして、ノエル様にはこちらの、
And for Noel-sama, we have this...
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
何だい、これ。
What's this?
ちょこのギリギリを守るために、特別に作られたモザイク棒です。
It's a mosaic wand specially made to protect Choco's risky parts.
特別！すげー！
Specially made! Awesome!
何だこれ、モザイク！来た！
What is this? A mosaic! It's here!
ボタンで、このモザイクの粗さを変えられるらしい。
Apparently, you can change the mosaic's density with a button.
今めっちゃ粗くなってるから。
It's really coarse right now.
あ、本当、薄くできる！
Oh, really, you can make it faint!
本当だ！
It's true!
すげー。でも粗い方がむしろ良いまであるな、これ。
Amazing. But it's almost better when it's coarse like this.
確かに。オッケー。
True. Okay.
隠すや。これ大丈夫かな？でも配信ね、ちょっと守りますよ。
Gotta hide it. Is this okay? We have to protect the stream.
ちょこの配信を守ってください。
Please protect Choco's stream.
頑張ります！
We'll do our best!
それでは撮影会、スタート！
Now then, the photo shoot starts now!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まずやっぱ全身。全身だよね。
First, we definitely need a full-body shot.
全身だよね、そう。そうだよね。
Full-body, yeah. That's right.
普通にこうね、ちょっとポーズ、いつものちょこ先生の、
Just a normal pose, like the usual Choco-sensei one,
こんな感じ。
Something like this.
あー！美しい！
Ah! Beautiful!
美しい！あー、あー！
Beautiful! Ah, ah!
良いね、良いね！
Nice, nice!
え、かわいい！もうここちょっとまずいんじゃない？ここ。
Eh, so cute! Isn't this part a bit too risky? Right here.
まずいかな？あ、何、逆に！
Is it risky? Oh, wait, the other way around!
え、逆に！ちょっと、ちょ、ノリノリなんですけど。
Eh, on the contrary! Wait, she's really getting into it.
まずいかな？あ、ちょっと、ちょ、ちょっとね。
Is it bad? Oh, wait, just a little.
ここ、揺れて、めちゃ、
It's shaking so much right here,
あ、モザイクが！モザイクが追いついてない！
Ah, the mosaic! The mosaic can't keep up!
追いついてない！
It can't keep up!
じゃ、ノエル様頑張って、頑張って！えいっ！
Come on, Noel-sama, keep it up, keep it up! Take that!
こうやってね、あー、こういう感じでね。うん、うん。
Like this, ah, in this way. Yeah, yeah.
あ、モザイク。あ、どんどん、どんどん、
Ah, the mosaic. Oh, keep it coming, keep it coming.
ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてみてもいいですか？
Could you try jumping for us?
ジャンプ確かに！すごい、プル、あ！
Jumping, for sure! Wow, the jiggle... Ah!
ヤバイヤバイヤバイ！ヤバイヤバイヤバイ！
Risky risky risky! Risky risky risky!
あかん、あかん、あかん、あかんでしょ、これ。
No, no, no, this is no good!
おいおいおい！
Hey hey hey!
あらー！え、ちょっとせっかくだから、
Oh my! Well, since we're here,
椅子とかも座っちゃう？
How about sitting in the chair too?
椅子？うん、椅子ね、ここにありますね。
The chair? Yeah, the chair is right here.
はーい。椅子。よいた。
Okay. The chair. There we go.
おー、良いね！靴もかわいい！
Ooh, nice! The shoes are cute too!
なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。
They're a bit bluish, aren't they?
あ、そう。ちょこね、そこが赤なの。
Oh, yeah. For Choco, the soles are red.
あ、えー！
Oh, what?!
ちょっと、ちょ、ちょ、まずい！ありがとうございます！
Wait, wait, wait, that's risky! Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
そこがね、赤なの、これ。ありがとうございます！
Right here, they're red. Thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！そう。
Thank you very much! Yeah.
大丈夫？あ、でもなんか見えてないからね。
Is it okay? Well, nothing's actually showing.
大丈夫です、大丈夫です。セーフです。
It's fine, it's fine. We're safe.
中は見えてないよ、守ってます。チャンネル守ってます。
Nothing's showing inside, I'm protecting it. Protecting the channel.
良いね、じゃあ、こう、どんどん、どんどん、上を見てもらって。
Nice, then keep looking up more and more.
あ、良いね！
Ah, nice!
あら、かわいい！見えてる？
Oh, so cute! Can you see?
見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
I can see, I can see!
見えてるよ！うーん！
I can see! Yeah!
あ、かわいい！かわいいね。
Ah, so cute! You're so cute.
おーい！かわいい！
Ooh! So cute!
あら。え、ちなみに、ラミィさん、あれですよ。
Oh. By the way, Lamy-san, there's also that.
この椅子に座って先生ポーズも、気持ち良いですけど。
Sitting in this chair and doing the teacher pose would be great too.
先生ポーズ取って欲しい。
I want you to do the teacher pose.
先生ポーズって何だ？こんな感じ？
What's a teacher pose? Like this?
あ、良い！良いですねー、良い！
Ah, nice! That's great, nice!
非常に良い！これ、もうモザイク要らないね、これ、これは。
Extremely nice! We don't even need the mosaic for this one.
非常に、非常に。
Extremely, extremely.
本当、本当、要らないのか、これ。
Really, really, do we not need it?
いや、わかんない、わかんない。ちょこ先生の魅力が溢れすぎてて。
No, I don't know, I don't know. Choco-sensei's charm is just overflowing.
良いですねー！
It's so nice!
素晴らしい！え、じゃあ団長も良いですか？
Wonderful! Well, can Danchou ask for one too?
何、何、何？
What, what, what?
お尻フリフリ、ちょっと、して頂きたいんですけど、ちょっとフリフリ。
I'd like to see some hip-wiggling, please, just a little wiggle.
えっと、後ろ向いてもらって、後ろ向いて、白衣越しだけど。
Um, turn around, turn around, even though it's through the lab coat.
フリフリ、あ、良いねー、フリフリ！
Wiggle, ah, nice, wiggle!
白衣越しだが、その下に、その、あ！ちょっとその下に、
Through the lab coat, but underneath that, um, ah! Underneath that,
スカート結構際どい！でもこれ、うん、
The skirt is pretty risky! But this, yeah,
白衣ってこれ、脱げ、脱いで欲しいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
As for the lab coat, I want you to take it off, can't you?
脱げるけど、メン限でって言ってた。
I can, but they said to save it for members-only.
あ、メン限なら脱いでくれるんですね！
Oh, so you'll take it off for members-only!
あ、良いね。え、ガニ股、あのココ会長リスペクトで、
Oh, nice. Well, how about the Ganimata pose, in honor of Coco-kaichou,
団長ガニ股好きなんで、はい！
Danchou loves the Ganimata pose, so come on!
うわー！はいっ！ガニ股さん！良いね！
Whoa! Here we go! Ganimata! Nice!
ガニ股助かる！ガニ股！
Ganimata is a lifesaver! Ganimata!
これちょっとモザイク！モザイク！ちょっと見えてるもんな。
We need the mosaic for this! Mosaic! Something's showing.
モザイクお願いします！モザイクが、無効から、
Mosaic, please! The mosaic is failing,
じゃ、ヤバイ！逆にヤバイ！
Wait, this is bad! It's actually worse now!
ヤバイヤバイヤバイヤバイ！ヤバイ！
Risky risky risky risky! Risky!
かわいいー！ふー！
So cute! Phew!
どんどん行こう、どんどん行こう。えーと、はい！
Let's keep going, keep going. Um, okay!
じゃあラストは、やっぱアイドルだからさ、
Then for the finale, since you're an idol after all,
ちょこせん、アイドル、とびきりのかわいいアイドル、お願いします！
Choco-sen, as an idol, give us your cutest idol look, please!
はいっ！
Okay!
えー！かわいい！
Oh! So cute!
いや、これは、あ、良いね！ウィンク！
Wow, this is... ah, nice! A wink!
可愛い！
Cute!
アップいい、顔のアップいい。たまらんです。
Up close! Up-close shots of her face are great! I can't get enough.
まぁ！
My!
たまらんです。
It's irresistible.
可愛い！
Cute!
おっけー。いっぱいいただいた。
Okay, we got plenty.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやちょっとね、この続きはちょっとね、メン限でやらせていただきますので。
Well, we'll be continuing the rest of this over in the membership-only stream.
♡このあとのメン限♡
アフターライブ
特別撮影会
シチュエーションドラマ2本
♡After this: Members-only♡
After-live
Special photoshoot
2 Situation dramas
メン限ではちょっと、歌も撮影会もシチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やっちゃいます！
In the membership stream, we'll have songs, a photoshoot, and even two situation dramas!
おー、楽しみだ。
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
え、ちなみにさ、なんかタイトルとかあんの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, do those situation dramas have titles?
あ、今回のタイトルが...
Ah, the titles this time are...
先生と...ベッドで...特別バレンタイン...っていうタイトルと、
『With Teacher in Bed, a Special Valentine』...
あー、特別！たまらん！
Ah, special! Irresistible!
先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン！
『With Teacher in Bed, a Special Valentine』!
...あと、診察室で甘い処方箋をっていう。
...and 『A Sweet Prescription in the Exam Room』.
♡シチュエーションドラマ♡
先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン
診察室で甘い処方箋を
♡Situation Dramas♡
With Teacher in Bed, a Special Valentine
A Sweet Prescription in the Exam Room
ああ〜、ママ〜！
Aah, Mama~!
最高すぎる。
This is way too good.
あの、目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて、
For the camera angle, we'll have the cameraman lie on the bed...
ちょっとみんなが本当に、あの、本当に見えるように、ちょこが覆いかぶさるように...
...so you can all see what it's like as Choco leans over you...
おおー！たまらん！
Ooh! Irresistible!
ちょっと、あ、ね、いろんな画角で撮っていただきたいと思います。
I want to try taking photos from various angles.
楽しみだな。
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだ。
Looking forward to it.
お楽しみに。
Please look forward to it.
ということで、そろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います。
And with that, our time is almost up, so let's head back to the live performance.
こんな気持ちでね、次ライブだった。
We're going into a live concert with this kind of mood?
そうだ。
That's right.
急げ！
Hurry!
急げ〜！
Hurry up~!
はい、というわけで。このあと二人それぞれちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど、
Alright, so after this, each of you will perform a duet with me,
ちょっとね、最後に三人でも歌うので楽しみにしてててください。
but all three of us will sing together at the very end, so please stay tuned for that.
楽しみ。
Exciting.
お楽しみに。
Look forward to it.
それでは着替えに行きましょうか。
Well then, shall we go get changed?
オッケー。
Okay.
あ、これ？
Oh, this?
すごい！カーテン、リボンも付いてる。
Wow! The curtain even has ribbons on it.
可愛い。
Cute.
じゃあ、ちょっとカーテンの裏で。
Let's go behind the curtain then.
裏ですか？
Behind here?
お願いしまーす。
If you would.
行ってきまーす。
Off we go!
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
そろそろそばに Baby
Better be close soon, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me darling
Melting away, catch me darling
ぴゅあぴゅあココアふわり
Pure, pure cocoa, drifting
ゆるゆるワンツー
Relaxed, one, two
なんか眠れない夜には
On nights when I just can't sleep
お散歩 特別パーティタイム
A stroll, special party time
二人きり やった
Just the two of us, yay!
あの角曲がればベンチしかない公園だよ
If you turn that corner, there's a park with only benches
蒸し暑い空気の中 迷い込むんだ
Getting lost in the humid air
コンビニちょっと寄り道
A quick stop at the convenience store
買い足し アイスじゃなくってこれがいい
Buying more, not ice cream, this is better
かき混ぜ ほろ酔いドリンクでストロング
Mix it up, a slightly tipsy drink, make it strong
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラムで潰してお願い
Liqueurs won't do anymore, crush me with rum, please
お砂糖山まし増しで 飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra, extra sugar, no need for it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして ぐびって飲んで
Melt it in the heat, and gulp it down
くせのある私のことを 大事にしてよね
Take good care of someone as quirky as me
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
そろそろそばに Baby
Better be close soon, baby
とろけちゃって Catch me darling
Melting away, catch me darling
ぴゅあぴゅあココアふわり
Pure, pure cocoa, drifting
ゆるゆるワンツー
Relaxed, one, two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely walk home
ふらふら特別ボーナスタイム
Floating along, special bonus time
手を繋ごう
Let's hold hands
大きめTシャツ 君に借りたありがとう
The oversized T-shirt I borrowed from you, thank you
匂わせみたいにして 困らせたいんだ
I want to hint at us and make you flustered
コンビニまた寄っちゃって 楽しい
Stopping at the convenience store again, how fun
もう一、本だけ 弱いやつ
Just one more, a light one
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ツルツル　リンネ　ベルベット　テンパリングが大事
Smooth, circular, velvet - tempering is important.
熱すぎても　飽きちゃって
If it's too hot, I'll get tired of it...
冷たいのはダメ　やだもん
...if it's cold, that's no good. I don't want that!
チョコみたいな私を　プレシャスにして扱って
Treat me like chocolate, treat me precious.
未炭酸のお酒で　シュワシュワシュワ
With non-carbonated liquor, fizz, fizz, fizz.
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless you tell it.
恋してるチョコにここでチュッして
Give this chocolate in love a kiss right here.
夜空のグラスに　キラキラこぼして
Spill some sparkles into the glass of the night sky.
息もできないくらいに
So much that I can't even breathe...
だって　だって　だって　だって
Because, because, because, because...
恋に溺れて
...drowning in love.
君の熱で溶けたら　そのまま食べてよ
If I melt from your heat, just eat me as I am.
手にベトベトついちゃって
My hands are all sticky...
一緒　一緒
...together, together.
完脳お酒　ほろ酔い　ウインクでストロング
Brain-saturating alcohol, tipsy, strong with a wink.
リキュールじゃ物足りない　ラブで尽くして　お願い
Liqueur isn't enough, please shower me with love.
お砂糖はマシマシで　飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra sugar please, I don't care if it's easy to drink.
灼熱でさ　溶かして　ゴクって飲んで
Melt it in the scorching heat and gulp it down.
クセのある私だからさ
Because I'm a handful...
君が選ばれた　サマーチョコレート
...you've been chosen, Summer Chocolate.
ドロドロトロリ　ベイビー　とろけちゃって　キャッチミーダーリン
Melty and gooey, baby, I'm melting, catch me darling.
ピュアピュア　ココアふわり
Pure, pure, cocoa fluffing up.
ツルツル　ワン・ツー！
Smooth, one, two!
Wassup Japan!
Can you hear me?
It's Reggaeton Choco.
No money no job.
To my barrios.
We are no reason to be sad.
It's time to get up.
We have a hot new song.
That's from AKB48.
To make you feel good.
Koisuru Fortune Cookie.
So dance Japan crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
作詞：秋元 康　作曲：伊藤 心太郎
Koisuru Fortune Cookie
Lyrics: Yasushi Akimoto / Music: Shintaro Ito
あなたのこと好きなのに
Even though I like you...
私には興味ない
...you have no interest in me.
何度目かの失恋の準備
Getting ready for another heartbreak...
Yeah Yeah Yeah
まわりを見れば大勢の
Looking around...
可愛い子たちがいるんだもん
...there are so many cute girls.
地味な花は気づいてくれない
No one notices a plain flower...
Yeah Yeah Yeah
カフェテリアに流れるMusic　ぼんやり聴いていたら
Listening absent-mindedly to the music playing in the cafeteria...
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ　つま先から動き出す
...before I know it, I'm moving to the rhythm from my toes.
止められない今の気持ち
I can't stop these feelings.
カモンカモンカモンカモンベイビー
Come on, come on, come on, come on baby.
占ってよ
Tell my fortune.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー　未来はそんな悪くないよ
In-love Fortune Cookie, the future isn't that bad.
Hey Hey Hey　ツキを呼ぶには
Hey Hey Hey, to call for luck...
笑顔を見せること
...just show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー　運勢今日よりもよくしよう
Heart's Fortune Cookie, let's make our luck better than today.
Hey Hey Hey　Hey Hey Hey
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't all that bad, right?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる　あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
A surprising miracle will happen, I feel we'll fall in love somewhere.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Koisuru Fortune Cookie (Fortune Cookie in Love)
あなたのことが好きなのに
Even though I love you...
私に自信がないの
...I don't have any confidence in myself.
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can already imagine your reaction.
Yeah yeah yeah
性格いい子がいいなんて
You say you prefer a girl with a good personality...
男の子は言うけど
...that's what boys always say, but...
ルックスがアドバンテージ
...looks are always an advantage.
いつだって可愛い子が
It's always the cute girls...
人気投票１位になる
...who come in first in the popularity polls.
Please please please oh baby
私も見て
Look at me too.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie in love,
その殻 さあ壊してみよう
Let's try breaking that shell!
Hey hey hey
先の展開 神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know what happens next.
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie of tears,
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative!
Hey hey hey
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is overflowing with love.
悲しい出来事 忘れさせる
It makes you forget the sad things.
明日は明日の風が吹くと
I think that tomorrow,
思う
the winds of tomorrow will blow.
Come on come on come on come on baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie in love,
未来は そんな悪くないよ
the future isn't that bad.
Hey hey hey
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
To call for luck, just show a smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie of hearts,
運勢 今日よりも良くしよう
let's make our luck better than today's.
Hey hey hey
人生 捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't so bad, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える
I have a feeling that somewhere,
予感
we can love each other.
Wooo!
初恋大戦争
作詞：Medansy (TRIPFRONTIER)　作曲・編曲：Yo-SK
Hatsukoi Dai-Sensou (First Love Great War)
Lyrics: Medansy (TRIPFRONTIER) / Composition & Arrangement: Yo-SK
君が好きったら君が好き
I say I like you, I like you!
あのね乙女は 本気出すと すごいんです
You know, when a girl gets serious, she's amazing.
1 2 いずれ 集中
1, 2, concentrate eventually.
あの手 この手で ライバルを出し抜くの
Outwitting rivals with this trick and that.
全部 計算ずみ レシピ通り
Everything is calculated, according to the recipe.
隙だって武器にして
Using openings as a weapon...
嘘ついてみたりして
...trying to tell a lie...
酔ったフリで甘えて
...acting drunk and being spoiled...
すでにデキてる
...it's already established.
あ、デコした
Ah, I decorated it.
つまみ食いしたらなくなった
It's gone because I snuck a bite.
並んで 日本酒
Japanese sake lined up.
時にファンキー
Sometimes funky.
苦いのはNGで
Bitter things are NG.
女の子の季節だもん 全部
It's a girl's season, so everything...
思い通りになってよね
...must go exactly as planned, okay?
君は私と 結ばれます
You will be united with me.
本命あげちゃう メルティ
Giving you my true love, Melty.
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
A Great War where I won't hand you to anyone.
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
I'm getting so excited, Merci.
それじゃ手を繋いじゃお 内緒のデート
Then let's hold hands, it's a secret date.
Sweety sweety kiss
甘くていいの
It's fine if it's sweet.
Sweety sweety heart
恋いなのがいいっしょ
Love is good, isn't it?
初恋なんだもん 絶対 譲らない
Because it's my first love, I'll never give in.
覚悟です 本気なのです
I'm determined. I'm serious.
目を見て言って 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me your feelings.
Girls' Battle Field
誰と喋ってるの？
Who are you talking to?
Girls' Battle Field
既読スルーがしょっぱい
Being left on read is bitter.
Girls' Battle Field
大丈夫 へこたれないもん
It's okay, I won't give up!
惚れさせた方が 勝ちです
The one who makes the other fall in love wins.
甘い物 全部 食べちゃいな
Go ahead and eat all the sweets.
砂糖の量は愛の量
The amount of sugar is the amount of love.
間違えた これ塩だった
Oops, I made a mistake, this was salt.
マーマレード
Marmalade!
ドキドキ ドキドキ してはいる
My heart is thumping, thumping.
真心込めて ラッピング
Wrapping it with all my sincerity.
自分も 本気コーデで行く
I'll go with my best outfit too.
祈る ラブ・チャージ
Praying, Love Charge!
何度も試作した
I made many prototypes
横練習もした
I practiced over and over
夜明けになどなるな
Don't let the dawn come
大丈夫 自分史上
It's okay, I'm the cutest version
一番可愛い私なんだから
of myself I've ever been
君は私と結ばれます
You and I will be together
結ばれる運命なのです
It is our destiny to be together
褒めあげちゃう メルティ
I'll shower you with praise, Melty
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
I won't let anyone have you, it's a great war
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
My heart is fluttering, Merci
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃう？
Then, shall we hold hands?
内緒のデート
A secret date
ツキツキきゅん 甘くていいの
Tsuki-Tsuki kyun, being sweet is fine
ツキツキはい。 こういうのがいいっしょ
Tsuki-Tsuki yes. This kind of thing is good, right?
初恋なんだもん
Because it's my first love
絶対譲らない覚悟です
I'm prepared to never back down
本気なのです
I'm serious
目を見て言って
Look into my eyes and say it
君の気持ち
Your feelings
Fiwa-la, fiwa-la, Fiwa-la, fiwa-la love
はい！ということで、チョコたち3人の新曲でした！
Hi! So, that was a new song from the three of us!
イェーイ！
Yay!
新曲でしたー！
It was a new song!
改めてまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にね、
Once again, with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama,
コラボ歌唱した「初恋大戦争」という新曲なんですけど
it's a new song called "Hatsukoi Daisensou" that we sang together.
今回作詞作曲をMEDANS様、そして
This time, the lyrics and composition are by MEDANS-sama, and
編曲をyou-ske様にお願いいたしました。
the arrangement is by you-ske-sama.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今回のテーマがバレンタインの日に
The theme this time is on Valentine's Day,
3人の可愛い女の子たちが、一人の男の子を
three cute girls, to get one boy,
手に入れるためにバチバチに出し抜こうとするみたいな...
try to outsmart each other intensely...
なるほど。激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております。
I see. It's a very sweet theme song.
いいね、可愛い。可愛い。
Nice, it's cute. So cute.
そう。3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングに
Yes. With our three voices combined, it's become a total idol song,
なっているので、ぜひぜひ皆様聞いてください！
so please, everyone, give it a listen!
聞いてね！
Listen to it, okay!
何回も聴きたいなあ。
I want to hear it many times.
ね、何回も聴きたい！ 2回目行けるところあるかな？
Right, I want to hear it over and over! Is there a place where we can hear it a second time?
こちらの楽曲は、この後24時から、
This song will be available from 24:00 tonight,
2月15日0時からね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
at 0:00 on February 15th, on various music sites!
やったー！聞ける！
Yay! We can hear it!
そしてね、この配信後すぐに、
And right after this stream,
この楽曲のMVが...
the MV for this song will be...
公開されます！
released!
イェーイ！やったー！
Yay! Hooray!
ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聞いて、MVの方にも
So please listen to it a lot, and for the MV,
ちょっと感想とかね、コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなって思います。
I'd be happy if you could leave some impressions and comments.
見てね！お願いします！
Check it out! Please!
じゃあね、二人とも、今日はありがとう！
Well, thank you both for today!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
嬉しい。ありがとう！
I'm so happy. Thank you!
引き続きね、頑張ってくださいね！頑張る！
Keep it up for the rest of the show! I will!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おさらばじゃ！
Farewell!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして、ここからライブ後半となります。
And from here, we move into the second half of the live performance.
まだまだゲストパートとか、なんと最後に
There are still guest parts, and at the very end,
重大告知もあるので、
there's a major announcement,
皆様一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
so let's all enjoy it together!
それでは、次のゲストはこちら！
Now then, here's our next guest!
大人なフリして。
Otona na Furi shite.
急に会いたいって いつものように準備してる
Suddenly you say you want to see me, I'm getting ready as usual
午前0時すぎの終電で向かうって返した
I replied that I'd head there on the last train after midnight
「やめておきなよ」って言われても
Even if I'm told "Better stop it"
また会いにいく 会いたいから
I'll go see you again, because I want to see you
大人だもん。
Adult-ish
別の人に落ちちゃう
I'll fall for someone else
街の風は少し冷たい
The city wind is a little cold
慣れないワイン 無理やり飲み干してしまっては
Forcing down wine I'm not used to...
フラ、フワ
Dizzy and lightheaded
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手しちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess things up?
少しの弱音もこぼしたくない
I don't want to show any weakness
ちょっと期待してね
Expect a little from me
ずっと見栄張ってね
Keep putting on a front
まわりばかり気にして生きてる
Living while only caring about what's around
ちょっと優越感
A bit of superiority
でもなんか寂しくてあぁ
But somehow I'm lonely, ah
本当の自分じゃない気がして
Feeling like it's not the real me
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Pushing myself even though it's not like that
味のしないキスでも
Even with a tasteless kiss
100倍一番嬉しくて
I'm a hundred times more happy
取り繕った私は 可愛いかな？
Is the fabricated me cute?
今夜は壊れるほど 抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I break
今にも切れそうな 糸で繋がってる恋だね
It's a love connected by a thread about to break
私が諦めたら きっと簡単に消えちゃうね
If I give up, it'll surely disappear easily
引き留めるにはどうする？
How can I make you stay?
ああ、不満だったらどうする？
Ah, what if you're dissatisfied?
不器用に指を絡めて
Clumsily intertwining our fingers
いつもチェックしてね
Always check on me
息苦しくしてね
Make it stifling
他の娘と比べてばっかりだ
You're always comparing me to other girls
一番見てほしい ああ
I want you to look at me most, ah
目の前のあなたは
You, right in front of me
どこか違う景色見てる
Are looking at some other scenery
いつも優しいふりして
Always pretending to be kind
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
Smiling even though it's not like that
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get
孤独はドクドク満ちて
The more loneliness fills me up
少しずつ離れて 言葉わかるよ
Bit by bit we drift apart, I understand the words
今夜は忘れるほど 抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I forget
自分はもっと強く なればさよなら
If I become stronger, then goodbye...
殻を言えるのにな
I could say it to the shell
いつもわかったふりして
Always pretending to understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
Pushing myself even though it's not like that
ふと見せる優しさが ずっと忘れられなくて
The kindness you occasionally show, I can't ever forget it
取り繕った私は 可愛いかな？
Is the fabricated me cute?
今夜は壊れるほど 抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I break
とうとう溢れだした目 私は頑張ったよね
Finally, my eyes overflowed, I worked hard, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると 思っていた もういいから
I thought you'd look my way someday, but it's enough now
取り繕った私は 泣かせゆく
I'll let the fabricated me cry
今夜は忘れるほど 抱きしめて
Hold me tonight until I forget
chocolate box
作詞・作曲：dezzy (一二三)
Lyrics/Composition: dezzy (Hifumi)
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always seem so sleepy
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
You always seem so bored
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
You always seem like you're in trouble
なんかいつもスマホ弄ってるし
You're always fiddling with your phone
本当はテンション高いのに
You're usually high energy
私といる時だけ低いし
But it's only low when you're with me
なんか自分ありえなくない？
Isn't that just unbelievable?
嫌い大嫌い どうでもいい
I hate you, I hate you, I don't care anymore
だったら僕も言うけどさ
Well, I've got things to say too
ちっちゃいことですぐ怒るし
You get mad at the smallest things
怒ったらずっと泣くし
Once you're mad, you cry forever
「ごめん」って言っても許してくれないし
Even if I say "sorry," you won't forgive me
その割にヤツが空けば
But on the other hand, if there's a gap
「結婚しようよ」とか言うし
You say things like "Let's get married"
ああ なんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person
ちくしょう もう知らないぞ
Dammit, I'm done with you
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love is
苦味の秘密のチョコレート
The secret chocolate of bitterness
二人だけ...
Only for the two of us...
二人だけのデコレーションを
With decorations just for the two of us
ちりばめて 彩って食べちゃおうか
Let's scatter them, color them, and eat them up
苦い苦い 愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
A mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If you warm it up and mix it, surely
いつかお口に合う味になるの
It'll eventually become a taste that suits your palate
ねえねえ そこいいかな
Hey, hey, is that spot okay?
なんで？
Why?
さっきはあのね ごめんね
Earlier, well, I'm sorry
なにが？
For what?
いつももやっとなるじゃん
It always gets all foggy, right?
それで？
And then?
今日はこれ渡したくて
I wanted to give you this today
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Because words aren't enough
だから？
So?
受け取ってくれないかな
Won't you please accept it?
なにを？
Accept what?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me
うわぁ
Whoa
なんだよそれ
What's that about?
あなたの優しさについつい甘えちゃう
I end up depending on your kindness
誰よりも近いから素直になれない
I can't be honest because we're closer than anyone
君の一生懸命さについつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting due to your hard work
誰よりも一番大好きだもんね
Because I love you the most of all
甘い甘い 夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure box of dreams
奇跡味のナイショのチョコレート
A secret chocolate with the taste of miracles
二人だけのイノベーションを
An innovation just for the two of us
探し組み立てたら賑やか
If we find and assemble it, it'll be lively
苦い苦い 日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter daily makeup box
世界味のナイショのチョコレート
A secret chocolate with the taste of the world
冷めきって割れないように
So it doesn't get cold and break
大事に包んで生涯の完成まで
Carefully wrapped until the completion of a lifetime
いつだって
Always
病める時も
Even in sickness
どんな時も
No matter when
そう ずっと
Yes, forever
健やかな時も
Even in health
手を取って
Taking your hand
違う二人を分かつまで
Until death do us part
愛してる
I love you
僕もそうさ
So do I
そばにいて
Stay by my side
そばにいる
I'll be there
なんて嘘かもよ
That might be a lie
ああ そうかい 僕も適当に言った
Ah, I see, I just said it randomly too
甘い甘い 苦い苦い
Sweet, sweet, bitter, bitter
甘い甘い 恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
A secret chocolate with the taste of the cosmos
二人だけのデコレーションを
With decorations just for the two of us
ちりばめて 彩って食べちゃおうか
Let's scatter them, color them, and eat them up
苦い苦い 愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
A mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたら絶対
If you warm it up and mix it, definitely
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
It'll eventually become the most happy taste
せーので
Ready, set...
Thank you so much
See you next time
ねえ 一つだけ聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask just one thing?
私のこと...
About me...
告白日和、です！
Confession Weather, isn't it!
会えるかな今日は 心が騒いで
Can I meet you today? My heart is racing
深呼吸したなら トキメキ踊る瞬間
After taking a deep breath, the moment excitement dances
私のことなど たぶん気にしてないの
You probably don't even care about me...
だけど ここにいるんだよ 私はここよ
But I'm right here, I'm right here
地面が揺れ動く 嫌われてないかな
The ground is shaking, I wonder if you hate me
意気込みでとにかく 挨拶だ
With all my determination, just a greeting!
やっと晴れたね ぱっと晴れたね
It's finally cleared up! It's suddenly cleared up!
そして元気になれ
And then, cheer up!
おはようの代わりに 背中を叩いて
Instead of saying good morning, I'll pat your back
さあ行くよ
Here we go!
やっと晴れたら ぱっと晴れたら
If it finally clears up, if it suddenly clears up
きっと元気な笑顔
Surely, a cheerful smile
なんだか今の この気持ちが 切なくなっちゃったよ
Somehow, this current feeling has become painful
授業は上の空 遠くを眺めたい
My mind is elsewhere during class, I want to stare into the distance
恋って甘いもんじゃない 苦いかも ください半分
Love isn't something sweet, it might be bitter, give me half
...目にみるだけに
...just to see it with my eyes.
触って確かめなきゃだから
So I have to touch it to make sure.
動き出そうよ　自分らしくね
Let's start moving, in our own way.
楽しく生きるの
Living happily,
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより勇気出そう
Instead of regretting what's unsaid, let's have courage.
ずっと前から　うんんと前から　聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting for a long, long time to ask you.
私から最初に伝えてしまえ　「大好きです」
I'll be the first to say it: "I love you."
ずっと前だよ　うんと前だよ　聞いたことに応えて
It's been a long, long time, so answer what I asked.
どんなふうに感じてるの？　全部見せてよ
How are you feeling? Show me everything.
楽しく生きるの
Living happily,
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
本当は不安でも勇気出そう
Even if I'm anxious, let's have courage.
行くよ！
Here we go!
うん！
Yeah!
ずっと前から　うんんと前から　聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting for a long, long time to ask you.
私から最初に伝えてしまえ　「大好きです」
I'll be the first to say it: "I love you."
ずっと前だよ　うんと前だよ　聞いたことに応えて
It's been a long, long time, so answer what I asked.
どんなふうに感じてるの？　全部見せてよ
How are you feeling? Show me everything.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢　胸を刺す
An arrow of light pierces my heart.
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you,
ねぇ　教えて
Hey, tell me.
世界は恋に落ちている
The World is Falling in Love
作詞・作曲: HoneyWorks
Lyrics & Composition: HoneyWorks
すれ違う言葉に　ちょっとだけの後悔
Just a bit of regret over our passing words,
涙こぼれて
Tears spill over.
忙しい感情　鼓動にリンクする
My busy emotions link with my heartbeat,
チューニング
Tuning,
確かめたいんだ
I want to make sure.
目的ばかりとらわれて　大事なものが霞んで逃げて
Caught up only in goals, important things fade and escape.
今日も盛りすぎた事
Things I've exaggerated again today.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢　胸を刺す
An arrow of light pierces my heart.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything,
ねぇ　聞かせて
Hey, let me hear it.
たった1ミリが遠くて
Just one millimeter is so far,
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days we ran through.
忘れない　忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget,
輝く1ページ
This shining page.
お似合いの二人に　なんだか複雑な
Watching the perfect couple, I have somewhat complex
気持ちがいるよ
Feelings.
集めた感情　鼓動にリンクする
Collected emotions link with my heartbeat,
体温計...
A thermometer...
自分のことは分からないまま
While still not understanding myself
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even ended up giving advice to that girl
胸が痛いや
My heart hurts
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢 胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces the heart
気付いたこの想いは
These feelings I've realized
もう遅いの
It's already too late
あの子の方が可愛いの知ってるよ だけど
I know she's cuter, but...
シンプルだけど 難しい
It's simple, yet difficult
上手くいかないでなんてね
Wishing for things not to go well
逃げ出したいくせに
Even though I want to run away
ねぇ、君のこと全部知りたいって思っちゃう。
Hey, I find myself wanting to know everything about you.
これが恋だって、初めて気づいたの。
I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい。
I definitely want you to look my way.
遅かったけど、諦めたくない。
It was late, but I don't want to give up.
だって... 好きだから
Because... I love you
春に咲いた花が恋をした
The flower that bloomed in spring fell in love
花は必死に上を向いて
The flower desperately looked up
笑った
And smiled
青い夏のつぼみも恋をした
The blue summer bud fell in love too
咲かない花と
The flower that wouldn't bloom
火薬の匂い
And the scent of gunpowder
本当の気持ち言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words
大事なこと話せたら
If I could talk about what matters...
今日もリスタート
Restarting again today
どんな悲しみだって
No matter what sadness it is
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud
今、君に伝えるよ
Now, I'll tell you
ねえ 好きです
Hey, I like you
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢 胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces the heart
全部知りたいんだよ
I want to know everything
ねえ 聞かせて
Hey, tell me
たぐり寄せて もう0センチ
Drawing closer, already 0 centimeters
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days that rushed by
忘れない 忘れられない
I won't forget, I can't forget
輝く1ページ
A shining page
はい、ということで！
Alright, then!
ここまでは、アキ様、ロボ子、
Up until now, Aki-sama, Roboco,
ござるにフータと一緒に歌わせていただきました！
Gozaru, and Fuuta sang along with me!
みんなありがとうー！
Thank you, everyone!
さてさて、ここからは、なんと重大告知が、
Now then, from here, there are surprisingly
2つあります！
two major announcements!
まずは1つ目が、こちら！ドーン！
First, here's the first one! Bam!
癒月ちょこ 誕生日記念 2026
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2026グッズ！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce them in a bit more detail!
まずは、こちら！
First, this one!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね、いやちょっとちょこの誕生日といえば、
Well, this, you know, speaking of Choco's birthday,
毎年Nardack先生ありがとうございますということで、
every year I say thank you to Nardack-sensei,
今年もNardack先生にめちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
and this year too, he has drawn a super wonderful illustration for us!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで、
The theme this time is Valentine's Day,
ちょっとね、チョコメイトを抱きながら、ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
so holding Choco-mate, I tried making it a chocolate-style cushion this time!
可愛いでしょ！
Isn't it cute!
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので、
The size is just about right for a pillow,
ちょっとねお昼寝の時とか仮眠用に、スヤァってできる、感じで使えちゃいます！
so you can use it for taking a nap or a quick snooze, like "Zzz"!
なんと、今回初めてちょっとね、
And surprisingly, for the first time,
お菓子が作れる、なんと、なんと
you can make sweets with a...
チョコのチョコレート型！
Choco chocolate mold!
耐熱も冷却も、あったかいのも
It's heat-resistant and coolable,
冷たいのも両方使えちゃって、
so you can use it for both hot and cold things,
ちょっとね、ショコラとチョコメイトの今回はチョコレート型になっております。
this time, featuring Chocolat and Chocomate in a chocolate mold.
まあ、マフィンとかね、クッキーとか、
Well, for muffins or cookies,
あとはまあ普通に冷やし固めてチョコレート入れたりとか、
or just letting chocolate set inside it,
なんか色々使えるから是非、みんなも作ってみてね。
it has many uses, so please give it a try.
そして続いてはこちら。
And next is this.
お待たせしました！チョコのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Thanks for waiting! The Choco Sleepy Plushie Keychain!
まあチョコといえばね、睡眠ということで、
Well, speaking of Choco, it's about sleep,
超ロングスリーパーのチョコが、今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって、
so I, the super long sleeper, am now a plushie keychain,
ちょっとすやすや祝ぐるみで、作らせていただきました。
created as a little sleepy plushie.
まあずっとね、肌身離さず持っていれば、いつか寝息が聞こえてくるかもしれない。
If you keep it close at all times, you might hear some sleeping sounds someday.
そして、今年もございます。
And we have them again this year.
癒月ちょこ書き下ろし台本の耳なめASMR台本！
Ear-licking ASMR scripts written by Yuzuki Choco!
録りましたよ、チョコのASMRボイス。
I've recorded them, Choco's ASMR voices.
今回ね耳なめの方は3つございます。
There are three ear-licking ones this time.
1つ目が、お出かけのチョコレート。
The first one is 'Outing Chocolate'.
いや、こちらはね、ちょっと、あの、皆様がご想像してるより、
Now, this one might be a bit more...
ちょっとあの、あの、えちちかもしれないんですけど、
well, 'naughty' than you're imagining,
まあ配信ではね、絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので、
it's a voice recording that I absolutely couldn't do on stream,
是非ともね皆様、ご購入して聞いてみてください。
so please buy it and give it a listen.
そしてもう1つが、残業後のご褒美デザートということで、
And another one is 'Reward Dessert After Overtime',
こちらはねチョコとの同棲シチュエーションとなっております。はい。
which is a living-together situation with Choco. Yes.
チョコが残業してきて帰ってきた時の、
It's about when Choco comes home from overtime,
うーん、まあデザートはチョコなのか、君なのか、どっちなんだろうね。
and whether the dessert is Choco or you... I wonder which one.
まあちょっと聞いてみてよ。
Well, you'll have to listen and see.
そしてそして、年下幼馴染のツンデレバレンタインということで。
And then, 'Younger Childhood Friend's Tsundere Valentine'.
今回はね聞いてる君たちが、
In this one, for those of you listening,
ちょっと隣の家のお兄ちゃんになった気分で聞いてみてください。
please listen as if you're the older brother next door.
こちらもね耳なめボイスとなっておりますが、
This is also an ear-licking voice,
なんとこちらドMの方は絶対に聞いていただけたら、
and I think if you're a masochist and listen to this,
ちょっとニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います。
it'll definitely make you grin.
はい。そしてそして、フルセットをご購入の方、
Yes. And for those who buy the full set,
フルセット購入特典、今回はなんと初めて、チェキ風ブロマイドカードになりました。
the bonus is a cheki-style bromide card for the first time.
ちょっとこちらね数量限定で、直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージが入っております。
These are limited quantity and include a handwritten signature and a foil message.
カキカキしちゃうよ。
I'll be writing them myself.
通常バージョンは箔押し複製サインと複製メッセージが入ります。
The standard version includes a foil-stamped signature and message.
そしてね、特典がもう一つ。
And there's one more bonus.
フルセット購入特典として、ヤキモチのギュッとASMRボイスが入っております。
As a full-set bonus, there's a 'Jealous Hug' ASMR voice.
いや、こちらはね、ちょっとあの、
Well, this one is a bit...
あまあまのギュッボイスなので。
it's a very sweet hugging voice.
まあちょっとね、普段あんまチョコ嫉妬しないんですけど、
Choco doesn't usually get jealous,
ちょっとまあ何に嫉妬してるかは聞いてからのお楽しみなんですけど、
so what I'm jealous of is a surprise for you to hear,
ちょっと是非是非ニヤニヤしながら聞いといてください。
but please enjoy it with a grin.
ぜひ手に入れてください！
Please make sure to get it!
そしてそして、重大告知二つ目は、
And now, the second major announcement is...
こちら！
this!
…ねぇ、ちょこたち　もう二度と会えないの？
...Hey, Choco and everyone, will we never meet again?
不思議ね　キミの言葉を聞くと　なんだか元気が出てきちゃう
It's strange. When I hear your words, I somehow feel energized.
もう一度、会いたいよ。大好きになってほしい。
I want to see you again. I want you to love me.
ねぇ、もしよければキミに……　ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしい。
Hey, if it's okay, I want you to... listen to Choco's memories.
「The Beginning」 12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース＆連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
'The Beginning' project start: 12 consecutive months of original song releases & linked voice dramas.
3/15 から毎月15日0時 オリジナル楽曲リリース
Original song releases on the 15th of every month at midnight, starting 3/15.
豪華アーティスト 参加
Participating major artists.
癒月ちょことあなたのストーリーを辿った全12話のボイスドラマ
A 12-episode voice drama following the story of Yuzuki Choco and you.
「The Beginning」 project 始動！
'The Beginning' project begins!
はい、というわけで、
Yes, and so,
えー！癒月ちょこ...
Yay! Yuzuki Choco...
12ヶ月連続オリ曲リリースが決定しましたー！
has decided to release original songs for 12 consecutive months!
The Beginning
2月15日からオリジナル楽曲12曲連続リリース (毎月15日0時リリース)
楽曲に連動したストーリーのボイスドラマ発売
豪華アーティストが参加
The Beginning
12-month consecutive original song release from Feb 15 (Released on the 15th every month)
Story-linked voice dramas will also be released
Featuring renowned artists
しかもこちら、なんとオリ曲に...
And what's more, for these original songs...
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが一緒にリリースされます！
story-linked voice dramas will be released together with them!
いや、こちらね、約1話から12話まで1曲ずつに連動して...
There will be voice dramas for each song, from episode 1 to 12...
ボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててくださーい！
so please look forward to it!
そして今回はね、その記念すべき1曲目を、これから披露したいと思います！
And now, I'd like to perform the first song of this project to celebrate!
それでは聴いてください。キミの秒針。
Please listen to 'Kimi no Byoushin'.
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back, once again...
愛おしさが増す
...the preciousness grows.
キミに 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
キミの秒針
作詞：ミズノゲンキ 作曲：関根佑樹(h-wonder)
Kimi no Byoushin
Lyrics: Genki Mizuno, Composition: Yuki Sekine (h-wonder)
キミから受け取った
A fragile story
壊れそうなストーリー
I received from you.
どこまでも広がる
The sky I looked up at,
仰ぎだした空
spreading endlessly.
変わらない毎日も
Even the unchanging days
色のない夢も
and colorless dreams...
手放して始めようよ
Let's let go of them and start anew.
不安の夜を数え
Even if it's a tomorrow faced
泣きながら迎えた
while counting anxious nights
明日でもいい
and crying, it's okay.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I've spread out the memories I carved.
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back, once again...
愛おしさが増す
...the preciousness grows.
キミに 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
二人で温めた
A precious story
大切なストーリー
we nurtured together.
どこまでも続いた
An endless path
果てない道
that went on forever.
疲れたら代わるから
'I'll take over if you're tired,'
そう言ってくれた
you told me.
優しさに触れて見えた
I could see it through the kindness I felt.
受け入れてくれたこと
I won't forget that you accepted me,
忘れない 嬉しくて 満ちた日
a day filled with joy.
雨上がりの胸に
Beautiful, like a rainbow appearing
架かった虹のように 綺麗な
in my heart after the rain.
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Every single word from you...
今も 宝物
...is still a treasure to me.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me,
輝けるこの気持ち 届けよう
let me deliver these shining feelings.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
I've spread out the memories I carved.
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back, once again...
愛おしさが増す
...the preciousness grows.
キミに 会いたいよ
I want to see you.
雨上がりの胸に
Beautiful, like a rainbow appearing
架かった虹のように 綺麗な
in my heart after the rain.
キミからの言葉 一つ一つが
Every single word from you...
今も 宝物
...is still a treasure to me.
はい、ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Alright, so, how did everyone enjoy it?
今回の新曲「君の秒針」は...
My new song, "Thy Second Hand,"
...志土の真央様が作詞...
...has lyrics by Shido no Mao-sama...
...そして二目飽様が作曲、編曲...
...and composition and arrangement by Nigume Aki-sama...
...そして編曲にはなんと、加藤貴之様も加わっていただきました！
...and Takayuki Kato-sama also joined in for the arrangement!
いや、今回は...
Well, this time...
...ボイスドラマ連動企画の第1弾として...
...as the first part of a voice drama collaboration project...
...ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、珠玉の楽曲に仕上がっております！
...it has turned into a gem of a song that serves as the theme song for the whole story!
ま、ドラマの鍵となるね、秒針というメタファーにも要注目してください！
Please also pay close attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which is key to the drama!
志土さんだけでなく、この後ね、豪華アーティストの皆様にもたくさん書いていただいたので...
Not just Shido-san, but many other wonderful artists have also written for this project...
皆様、リリースをお楽しみに！
...so everyone, please look forward to the release!
こちらの「君の秒針」は、各音楽サイトは...
This song "Thy Second Hand" will be on various music sites...
...ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
...it'll be a little while, but it's scheduled to be released on March 15th at midnight!
ま、ちょっとね公開まで時間が空くから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してみてください！
Since there's some time until the release, please re-watch this stream many times until then!
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it over and over!
そして、そして...
And also...
MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしててくださーい！
The MV will be released at a later date, so please look forward to it!
ということで、今日のチョコの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
So, how was Choco's birthday live today?
ま、この後は...
Well, after this...
...すぐに、冒頭、最初の方でお披露目した...
...immediately, as I announced at the beginning...
...ノエルちゃんとラミたんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があって...
...there will be the MV release of "Hatsukoi Daisakusen" with Noel-chan and Lami-tan...
そのあと、メン限で...
And after that, in the member-only stream...
♥このあとのメン限♥
♥Coming up for Members♥
...ちょっとライブと、撮影会の続きとか...
...we'll have a bit more live and the continuation of the photo session...
アフターライブ / 特別撮影会
After Live / Special Photo Session
...ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので...
...and situation dramas that you can only see there, among other things...
シチュエーションドラマ2本
2 Situation Dramas
(朝食inベッド？泥沼ランチ？絶対見逃せない（かも) )
(Breakfast in bed? Messy lunch? You can't miss it! (Maybe))
ぜひぜひ、気になる人は見に行ってください！
So if you're interested, please do come and watch!
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, I'll see you later!
お疲れいとは〜ん！
Otsukarei-to!